ABOUT ME

A demand generation, lifecycle, product marketing, and marketing ops professional with 12+ years of experience across B2C and B2B tech companies. Looking for a senior marketing position where I can make the most revenue impact.

Soft Skills	Hard Skills		Software	
People management	Forecasting & planning	Analytics: SQL, Excel	Google Suite	Outreach
Hiring & developing	Demand generation	Pricing & packaging	Salesforce	Drift
Strong presentation &	Product marketing	Lifecycle marketing	Marketo & Braze	LeanData
communication experience	Sales & marketing ops	Partnership marketing	Mode & Looker	Fivetran

EXPERIENCE

Co-Founder, StandardCode (YC Summer 2021)

May 2021 - May 2022

Founded StandardCode and went through the Summer 2021 batch of Y Combinator and backed by Soma Capital, Global Founders Capital and a number of angel investors. We focused on creating an API that helped companies comply with child data privacy laws around the world.

We successfully raised a \$2MM+ seed round and had a few beta customers before pivoting based on market feedback. We explored other ideas including a financial savings product for teens as well as a tool for Customer Success and Sales to be faster at outbound prospecting.

- Lead outbound marketing and prospecting efforts across verticals such as EdTech, mobile gaming, Web3, professional sports, fintech, and B2B SaaS
- Landed discovery calls and demos across SMB, Mid-Market, and Enterprise customers
- Created brand and positioning material based on user research and sales conversations
- Created our marketing and sales tech stack using Airtable, Apollo.io, and Google Sheets
- Created sales enablement material and competitive landscape research to accelerate the pipeline

Head of B2B Marketing, Remind

December 2015 - May 2021

Remind is the largest communication platform in K-12, funded by First Round Capital, Social + Capital, Kleiner Perkins, and Owl Ventures.

Helped grow the company from \$0M to \$20MM across four years. Started as a Senior Product Marketing Manager working on our first monetization efforts before the enterprise product existed. Responsibilities included positioning, branding, GTM launch, and pricing.

Our enterprise product, focused on school and district administrator tools gained traction and I was promoted to Head of B2B Marketing to focus on growth and operations. I built a team and process around GTM for our entire enterprise offering. Responsibilities included building and scaling a demand generation engine, hiring and training our first SDRs, BDRs, and account executives, developing lifecycle marketing programs, experimenting with growth channels, and building our marketing and sales ops infrastructure.

- Created and grew the B2B marketing function (demand gen, lifecycle/customer marketing, marketing operations) and seeded the BDR teams
- Created, implemented, and managed our marketing/sales tech stack including Marketo, Salesforce, LeanData, and Outreach resulting in zero slippage of leads worked
- Implemented data flows throughout the stack and created custom views, reports, and dashboards for sales and
 marketing to prioritize leads and accounts, and automate personalized outreach which lead to an increase in
 prospect reply rate and ultimately discovery calls booked
- Set up automated triggered campaigns based on product data (Product Led Growth) to touch prospects at the right time which increased conversion rate from MQL to SQL
- Implemented lead scoring and quality frameworks to ensure prioritization and timely follow-up by sales reps
- Ran early operations for our tutoring vertical which brought in 1MM in its first year
- Partnered with 20+ education and entertainment companies including Quizlet, Discovery Kids, and PBS to deepen
 engagement with our core messaging product
- Managed goal setting, OKRs, and leads forecasting for the Marketing team
- Ran leadership development programming for new managers across the company

EXPERIENCE CONTINUED

Growth & Product Projects, HireReady

February 2015 - December 2015

Worked on two entrepreneurial projects as founder that scaled to a few thousand users.

HireReady was the common app for the gig economy. Clients included Homejoy, Flour & Water, Kokio food truck. Stork was a text-based Q&A service for expecting parents to connect with doulas, nurses, and lactation consultants.

- · Ran sales, partnership, and marketing
- Conducted user research with dozens of parents and gig workers
- · Scaled top of funnel interest via Craigslist advertising, LinkedIn advertising, Facebook advertising, and Reddit
- Created partnerships with several unemployment agencies in the San Francisco Bay Area to help their clients get placed with jobs
- Created the marketing site while optimizing for signups

Growth Manager, Homejoy (acquired by Google)

December 2012 - February 2015

Homejoy is a home services marketplace funded by Y Combinator, Google Ventures, and Redpoint Ventures.

Joined Homejoy as the 2nd full-time employee. Started out as a city launcher, growing supply and demand in each of the first 20 U.S. markets before hiring a team under me to open the rest. Transitioned to a growth position where I created our lifecycle and retention programs for our demand and supply side using Oracle's Responsys marketing automation platform.

- Launched 30 markets domestically in 18 months and created the playbook to scale further
- Opened up markets in Canada, leading legal and operational international expansion
- Hired and trained 30 local market GMs and 2 additional city launchers
- Grew the P&L of the Midwest markets to \$5MM in bookings
- Implemented Responsys and created engagement and retention email programs which drove higher conversion rates and LTV
- Experimented with channels like direct mail using customer data to improve targeting
- Brokered a partnership opportunity with Clorox and presented to their management team

Business Development, Nutraclick (d.b.a. Force Factor)

January 2010 - September 2012

Nutraclick is one of the largest online direct response marketing companies selling health and beauty products.

Owned the P&L for one of Nutraclick's flagship brands, Force Factor, which is a line of health supplements aimed at men. Responsibilities included supply chain management, product development, and contract negotiations with retailers.

- Launched 5 products (~10 SKUs) with online and in-store distribution from formulation to promotion.
- $\bullet \quad \text{Sourced and negotiated contracts with packaging and product formulation vendors} \\$
- Negotiated and launched in-store promotions with GNC, Bodybuilding.com, Walmart, and Walgreens, winning several retailer awards like GNC's Rising Star and Bodybuilding.com's Brand of the Year
- Launched online and offline experiments to boost subscription LTV, boosting retention by an additional month and cross-selling revenue by 10%

EDUCATION Alum Bachelor of Science

Y Combinator Computational Biology

Summer '21 Massachusetts Institute of Technology

REFERENCES

Available on request